http://www.wintick.com/home/privacy

since 1994
TESTIMONIALS
Trustpilot Reviews
Toggle navigation
HomeFree Webinars FAQs SolutionsProductsAbleTrend 30-Day Trial AbleTrend 7.0 Stand Alone (stand alone trading system)AbleTrend Add-on for eSignal AbleTrend Add-on for NinjaTrader ASCTrend 3.5 (indicator packages for TradeStation users)AbleTrend Mobile WinTick (15-min delayed signals)AbleTrend Portfolio Performance (APP) Money Management (MM)Data (real-time data feeds)AbleData Data Module Access (DMA)Price/OrderAbleTrend 30-Day Trial AbleTrend Lease or Buy ASCTrend 3.5 (indicator packages for Tradestation users)AbleTrend Mobile WinTick (15-min delayed signals)AbleTrend Portfolio Performance (APP) Data (real-time data feeds)AbleData Data Module Access (DMA)Software Maintenance (for permanent users)DownloadsAbleTrend 7.0 AbleTrend addon for NinjaTrader 8 AbleTrend addon for eSignal AbleTrend Mobile ASCTrend 3.5 (for TradeStation users)WinTick Mobile About UsContactMember
Blogs
WinTick
PRIVACY NOTICE:
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on applications, forms or otherwise; and
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others.
We may disclose all of the information that we collect, as described above. However, to the extent such information is provided to a nonaffiliated third party, we will do so subject to an agreement that prohibits the third party from disclosing or using the information other than to carry out the purposes for which we disclose the information.
We may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to the following types of third parties:
financial service providers, such as securities broker-dealers, futures commission merchants, introducing brokers, commodity trading advisors and commodity pool operators;
non-financial companies, such as retailers, direct marketers and publishers; and
other non-affiliated parties as permitted by law.
We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf, or to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements.
The categories of nonpublic personal information that we disclose, as described above, and the categories of third parties to whom we disclose it are the same for former as for current customers.
If you prefer that we not disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties you may opt out of those disclosures; that is, you may direct us not to make those disclosures (other than disclosures permitted or required by law). If you wish to opt out of disclosures to nonaffiliated third parties, you may click here for the appropriate form.
On an internal basis, we authorize access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide services to you or to enforce our rights relating to your transactions with us. We maintain security practices and procedures to ensure the confidentiality of your nonpublic personal information.
3rd Parties
Risk Disclosure: Futures and forex trading contains substantial risk and is not for every investor. An investor could potentially lose all or more than the initial investment. Risk capital is money that can be lost without jeopardizing ones’ financial security or life style. Only risk capital should be used for trading and only those with sufficient risk capital should consider trading. Past performance is not necessarily indicative of future results.
Hypothetical Performance Disclosure: Hypothetical performance results have many inherent limitations, some of which are described below. no representation is being made that any account will or is likely to achieve profits or losses similar to those shown; in fact, there are frequently sharp differences between hypothetical performance results and the actual results subsequently achieved by any particular trading program. One of the limitations of hypothetical performance results is that they are generally prepared with the benefit of hindsight. In addition, hypothetical trading does not involve financial risk, and no hypothetical trading record can completely account for the impact of financial risk of actual trading. for example, the ability to withstand losses or to adhere to a particular trading program in spite of trading losses are material points which can also adversely affect actual trading results. There are numerous other factors related to the markets in general or to the implementation of any specific trading program which cannot be fully accounted for in the preparation of hypothetical performance results and all which can adversely affect trading results.
Testimonial Disclosure: Testimonials appearing on this website may not be representative of the experience of other clients or customers and is not a guarantee of future performance or success.
© Copyright 1995-2020 AbleSys Corporation. All rights reserved.
Privacy Statement
Address: 8407 Central Avenue Suite 1882, Newark, CA 94560
